[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "Does somebody die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "Yes, somebody died.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers Morgan"]}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", ":", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Could you give me your thoughts on that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "That was always my -- that was always my intention to become the new Piers Morgan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Howard, it doesn't get better than that, does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "First of all, your read was impeccable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Parents Television Council"]}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Parents, Teacher Council or something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "The Parents Television Council.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Teacher Council"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Is that right, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Completely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "And people say to me, what's their talent, and I guess they'll throw the same thing at you and say, all right, you're a good deejay but what else do you do, and the reality is you don't have to go to the sun to know it's hot, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sharon"], "PERSON": ["Howie"]}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Would you like to clarify that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Yes, I think it goes back to what I was saying before that, you know, I think a lot of times Howie and Sharon, you know, pick someone just to kind of annoy you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howie Mandell"]}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Do you have any advice for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Yes, I would avoid Howie Mandell like the plague, would be my main advice to you .", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Claire Danes"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "``", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Who's on next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "I'm interviewing Claire Danes from \"Homeland \"who I think is one of the great acting talents in America right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Mr. Crowley, what are your thoughts as the Iraq war ends?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Well, it was an extraordinary effort, Piers, and perhaps, you know, on -- at one level it was nine years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Crowley"], "LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Does that make the war in your view potentially an illegal conflict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "That's a very good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bradley Manning"], "LOCATION": ["Quantico"]}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "What are your feelings about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "ROWLEY: Well, you know, eight months ago I thought that Bradley Manning's treatment out of Brig in Quantico was a distraction and was actually undercutting the unnecessary prosecution.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", ":", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Do they feel once it was clear the weapons of mass destruction didn't actually exist that it was a legitimate conflict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "What was really extraordinary about those three USO tours was that it was probably one of the most -- really probably -- I was profoundly, you know, changed by it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "It is disappointing if Donald Trump really doesn't run that we could miss out on President Trump, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Yes, I think -- I think that we have to as a people reclaim a certain kind of rationality when it comes to candidates.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Donald Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Because Herman Cain was, from a comedic point of view, gold dust, wasn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "MD", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "He's stellar.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Newt Gingrich"]}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Only to really examine whether you feel being accused of being too zany, and this seems certainly an appropriate question for you, Lewis, one of the zaniest man in America, is being zany a criteria for not being taken seriously as a president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Well, I mean, zany is not a word I'd use for Newt Gingrich.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lewis"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "How much of this -- and I really want the answer to be a lot -- how much of her is in you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ":", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Um, we're both phony blonds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "The more successful the show has got, that that kind of issue becomes very, oh, ok, better be careful here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RBR", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "RBR", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "I just finished filming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "How exciting is that for you from an acting point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "It's wonderful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "If you're about to do it, OK, what would you want the other person to say, like right before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "This won't take long.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Don't I know you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "No, for real.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Terrifying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "No, that's not true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Is this true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "ANES: It wasn't overtly offered to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "What else did you get into?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Well, I had a very -- I had a steady boyfriend at the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Do you love it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Have you got better at dealing with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Paparazzi are difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "What are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "It's a machine I just made!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "You've racked up some awards, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "That was an intense run.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Was it love at first British sight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Um, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "And you've been married what, two years now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "Yes, two years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Your toes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Who gets the more jealous about the love scenes the other ones have to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "It's miserable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "It is, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "Do you want to yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "Yes -- eventually, I'd love that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["McGee"]}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Getting broody yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "Look at you, pokey, pokey McGee.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "See how I used that shamelessly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "We'll see.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "ORGAN: So what's left, \"Homeland,\" presumably there will be another series of \"Homeland,\" right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "We're doing another season.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Oh, you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "Yes, yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "See how it easy it is to get that stuff out there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]